It's a common mistake to only test the app in the best case use scenarios,
人们会经常犯一种错误 就是只在最理想的使用场景中测试应用
such as in our home or in our office where we're writing our code and
比如家里或办公室里 我们在这些地方写代码
we have a really good Internet connection.
并且拥有流畅的 Internet 连接
But as professional Android developers, it's important to take into account and
但作为专业的 Android 开发人员 有必要考虑到我们的应用会在一些
test the worst case or edge case scenarios in which our app will be
不理想或模棱两可的情况下使用 发生预料之外的状况
used and perhaps behave unexpectedly.
我们要对这些情况进行测试
Sometimes this means that our app may be used in places where there's a spotty
有时这意味着我们的应用 可能会在网络不稳定的地点使用
Internet connection and that's where a loading indicator,
在这种情况下 我们添加进去的
such as the one we added in, comes in as a great way to let the user know that
加载指示 有助于用户了解
we're still working on the request.
请求仍在进行中
It's also possible that the user will be in a place with no Internet
有时用户 还可能处于
connection at all.
完全没有　Internet 连接的地点
So what happens then?
这种情况要怎么办？
Does the app appear blank or does it unexpectedly crash?
应用会显示空白 还是意外崩溃呢？
Well, building a polished user experience
构建一个良好的 用户体验
means handling all of these edge cases.
意味着要处理所有这些边缘情况
Now I want you to examine the current behavior of the quake report app when we
现在请检查一下 目前 Quake Report 应用
have no Internet connection.
在没有 Internet 连接时的行为
We can test this by turning on Airplane Mode on a device.
我们可以开启设备的飞行模式 进行测试
When you go on airplanes, you usually turn on this mode.
通常在搭乘飞机时 开启该模式
Airplane Mode disables Wi-Fi, Bluetooth and cellular connectivity,
飞行模式会禁用 Wi-Fi 蓝牙和移动网络连接
meaning the device is now offline.
意味着设备处于离线状态
Pull down the notification shade and under the Quick Settings,
拉下通知菜单 在快速设置 (Quick Settings) 中
turn on Airplane Mode, then you should see an airplane icon in the status bar.
开启飞行模式 (Airplane Mode) 然后 在状态栏中即可看到飞机图标
If your version of Android looks different, you can also find this option
如果你的 Android 版本不一样 也可以在设置 (Settings) 应用中
in the Settings app underneath the section Wireless and Networks.
无线与网络 (Wireless and Networks) 下 找到该选项
See the link below for more help.
可以参照下面的链接获取更多帮助
Now go ahead and kill the app using the Resets menu, and
现在 请使用 重置 (Resets) 菜单关闭应用
then start it up from scratch.
然后重新启动它
When that happens, what do you see in the app?
重新启动后 应用中会出现什么？
Go ahead and write your answer in this text box.
请在文本框中 写下你的答案
When you're done, browse around other apps and
写完后 请浏览其他应用并查看
check what happens when there is no Internet connectivity.
没有 Internet 连接时 会发生什么情况
If you find any particularly good or bad examples,
如果发现任何 正面或反面示例
feel free to share them on the discussion forum linked below the quiz.
请使用测验下面的链接 分享到论坛上